demondemon.com 2016-10-19

# Privacy Policy - Scritty's SEO Blog

**Our Privacy Policy**

(last update: Apr 2012)   
****

## Information we gather

The following information may gathered from our website visitors for statistical purposes only:   
– IP address   
– Blog comment name (for users who wish to comment on any of the posts) 

## How we use the information we gather

We use the information to enhance your visitor experience.   
The use of a name for blog commenting is optional. We accept pen-names and pseudonyms as long as they are not offensive.   
IP addresses are held temporarily to measure visitor levels and to prevent site abuse from those who would look to spam our blog 

## The people that are given access to this information

Your personal information is accessible by the site admin only   
The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information

To safeguard your personal information, we secure these files under a double password system. The individual IP details are deleted on a six week rolling cycle.   
We fully comply with EU and US data protection and personal privacy laws.   
No personal data that could relate a site visit to any individual is kept   
If you have any questions please access our query page at; <http://www.demondemon.com/contact-info>

## Our use of cookies

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
